(Neighing)
Nice to see you.
(Nice to see you.)
We'll bring in the star
of the Rainbow Live.
To celebrate 2026,
the Year of the Red Horse,
we began a new project,
Rainbow Running Horses.
- Do you remember?
- Yes.
He's the second star
of Rainbow Running Horses.
He's the bassist
of a Korean rock band, Crying Nut,
and also the living legend who ruled
the golden era of indie music.
Let's sing it together.
One, two, three, four.
(Let's run)
Here's Han Kyung Rok!
(Han Kyung Rok)
(Shaking)
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
(Any proud Korean
would recognize the intro...)
(of "Luxembourg.")
(Isn't that good?)
("Isn't That Good?")
("Deep in the Night")
("Circus Magic Clowns")
(And the singer of "Let's Run")
(The generator of amazing songs)
(Crying Nut's Bassist Han Kyung Rok)
Nice to meet you.
- Rock and roll.
- Kyung Rok.
- My gosh.
- Say hello to our viewers.
- Sure.
Hello.
It's the Year of the Red Horse.
And no band fits the year
better than Crying Nut.
My name is Han Kyung Rok.
Nice to meet you.
(I'm Han Kyung Rok of Crying Nut.)
Then were you also born
in the Year of the Horse?
I wasn't born
in the Year of the Horse.
I was born in 1977.
Snake!
- I'm the same age as you. Yes.
- Snake! Yes.
- Come on. Yes.
- I'm happy to meet a friend.
- Same here.
- Oh, they're the same age?
- We've never met before.
- Oh, yes.
- Right.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
By the way, I was born
in the Year of the Snake too.
- We have the same zodiac animal.
- Yes, another snake.
- Snake.
- Yes.
(Deep in the snakes)
You can't do things like that here.
Deep in the snakes
(Fascinated)
"Deep in the snakes."
That line doesn't make sense.
Right.
- Don't say nonsensical things.
- But...
- I like that.
- I'll only say logical things.
- Let's begin our new project,
- Yes.
- "Running Horses."
- I'm...
I'm still on that line,
"deep in the snakes."
(Deeply affected)
- That was legendary.
- Listen.
(If you want,
I'll give you an encore.)
- Hey, that's...
- Yes!
(The audience is satisfied.)
It looks like
he's struggling to blend in here.
The second star of Running Horses...
is Han Kyung Rok. Let's take a look
at his Rainbow Live.
Rainbow.
Let's run together.
Rock and roll, come on!
(Let's run together.
Rock and roll, come on!)
I love it.
I can't get used to his style.
It looks like
I'm rocking the opening segment.
My gosh.
(The Year of the Red Horse)
(Rainbow Running Horses)
- "Captain Rock."
- Rock.
(Kyung Rok is sleeping,
covered in the blanket.)
(Swinging)
(He gives the blanket a good kick.)
(Groaning)
(Banging his head in his sleep)
- He's adorable.
- My gosh.
(Stretching)
- Oh, my. He's flexible.
- He's super flexible.
I've been holding an instrument
for 30 years.
- So my back is all out of shape.
- I bet.
So I've been taking Pilates classes
for two years.
(Grabbing)
- They're smart curtains.
- Smart curtains.
They're motorized curtains.
(Bright sunlight falls
on the dark rocker's face.)
(Rubbing his face)
He has a thick head of hair.
Hello. I've been living alone
for 20 years.
I'm a bassist of Crying Nut.
My name is Han Kyung Rok.
Nice to meet you.
(Crying Nut wrote timeless classics
recognized by everyone.)
(Source: Crying Nut)
(And this is where it all began.)
(In 1993,)
(Crying Nut was formed.)
(In 2001, Incheon
International Airport opened...)
(and Crying Nut released
"Deep in the Night.")
(Source: Ssamzi Sound Festival)
(Source: Crying Nut)
(From the underground scene
to the legendary band)
(The history of indie rock bands)
(Bassist of Crying Nut,
Han Kyung Rok)
They made their debut during
the Kim Young Sam presidency.
I was born in 1997. So that's...
- It was before you were born.
- Yes, that's right.
When you were born,
he had to face the economic crisis.
Right. The economic crisis
took place in 1997.
- It was really tough.
- How many presidents...
have l lived through?
(The legendary band, Crying Nut,
was formed 33 years ago.)
(The current time is 9:05am.)
(Getting up)
He got up in a cool way.
(Gosh, it's chilly.)
(He grabs the drying rack
as soon as he gets up.)
All right.
(Setting it up next to his bed)
All right. My gosh.
- Why put the blanket on the rack?
- What's going on?
I sweat a lot during the night.
It's too humid.
The blanket gets wet.
- You're drying it.
- You disinfect it in the sun.
Yes. I'm disinfecting it.
(He sun-dries the blanket
as soon as he wakes up.)
(Looking disheveled)
Gosh, his house...
(Past the foyer,)
(there's a fancy living room.)
I thought you'd live
in a semi-basement unit in Hongdae.
I used to have
the rock spirit before.
He's a rocker. So I assumed
there would be broken bottles.
- A lot of people assume that.
- Yes.
I thought there would be
punch marks on the walls too.
(A clean interior,
free of any punch marks)
(Chairs in different colors)
- That's cute.
- It's so cute.
(Decor items arranged
to his personal taste)
This shows why
personal tastes are so important.
I thought there would be writing...
- on the walls in paint.
- Like graffiti?
It's so clean and neat
for a rocker's house.
- Right.
- Right?
(Thinking)
I don't see any rebellious spirit
in your house.
Right.
- I take care of that when I'm out.
- Outside?
Your house is covered
with capitalism.
- Do you know what's fascinating?
- Yes?
The sentiment from Hongdae
still remains in his house.
- Where?
- Right.
Look at his lamp.
It's the way he arranged
the furniture in his house.
It reminds me of...
a successful musician's studio
in Hongdae.
(His personal taste is reflected
in the interior design.)
His house is so colorful.
I like this vibe.
(Plants are seen
throughout his house.)
It's so different from the house
I had in mind.
- Same here. I'm quite surprised.
- My gosh.
I realized something
after moving into this house.
Over 50 percent of interior design
goes into lighting.
Lighting sets the overall vibe.
(His house is unusually filled
with light sources.)
The stained glass lamp
is so beautiful. It's this one.
- Oh, this one.
- It's got a nice vibe.
(The lamps brighten
the atmosphere of his house.)
Is this a church?
- A church?
- Yes.
I wanted the church
and cathedral vibe.
- We see that at cathedrals.
- When colorful lights pour...
into the house, it sets a holy vibe.
Lighting is very important to me.
When I gaze at someplace bright,
I get this sense of warmth
for some reason.
It comforts me
in a gentle and soft way.
My house now faces southeast.
That's why it's very well-lit.
I lived in Hongdae for 20 years.
Actually, Hongdae...
is my turf.
So I have a lot of friends...
and shops in Hongdae.
So when I stepped out of my house,
it was like being in Las Vegas...
or at an amusement park.
I had so much fun every day.
Every day was a party.
So when I thought about it,
I had been performing for 30 years.
But for the first time in my career,
I left Hongdae.
Then I moved to Goyang.
I guess you can sort of say...
I exiled myself here.
So I moved to a different area.
I've been living here
for about seven months now.
I think I lived in Hongdae...
- longer than in my hometown.
- Yes, you did.
Where did you grow up?
- Dongbuichon-dong, Seoul.
- Dongbuichon-dong?
- You lived in a fancy neighborhood.
- It doesn't suit you at all.
It's different from a rock spirit.
- No, there was a spirit back then.
- Really?
I started off my career
in Hongdae too.
- Really?
- Yes.
My place was
around Yeonnam Police Box.
- Around there?
- Same here.
I lived in a semi-basement unit...
- in Sangsu-dong with Mal Nyeon.
- What?
I'm also from Sangsu.
- For some reason, I thought...
- I bet we brushed past each other.
- I must live in Hongdae to do art.
- Hongdae.
(Trudging)
(He puts on music
as soon as he wakes up.)
It's an LP record.
I wonder what kind of music
he'll listen to.
What?
(The rocker listens to
classical music in the morning.)
It's by Bach.
It's a completely different vibe.
I like listening to classical music
in the morning.
Hi, Rock Pup. Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
(Rock Pup, a pet doll)
- The one from IKEA.
- That's right.
(Turning on)
Gosh. You must be excited.
Let's eat.
The fish look cute.
(A morning greeting
to the school of his pet fish)
How long have you had them?
It's been about two years.
Here comes the tasty meat.
They're having a blast.
(After feeding the fish...)
(Grabbing)
What's that?
(Smelling)
It smells great.
Musicians love flowers.
- Right.
- Most of us do.
(Heading to the kitchen
while carrying the vases)
(The rocker starts his morning
with flowers.)
I've been growing flowers
for 20 years.
I had always liked flowers
ever since I was a kid.
I bought flowers
for my friends for no reason...
while walking on the street.
I do that. I like flowers.
That's romantic.
Flowers are romantic.
(Smiling)
Even the vases look beautiful.
I change the water in the vases
every morning.
I did it this morning too.
One must be diligent...
- to grow plants and flowers.
- Right.
- I'm impressed.
(After taking care of
his fish and flowers,)
(he lies down in the living room.)
I have a daily routine.
You're on a foam roller.
Yes. I love stretching
on foam rollers.
- You're quite flexible.
- Yes.
(Rolling)
He has two foam rollers.
It's like watching a circus.
(Laughing)
That's the most well-lit spot...
in my house.
It feels
as if the sunlight cleansed my soul.
I can feel my soul getting cleansed.
It's a routine for actresses.
What's up with your daily routine?
He's so different from rockers...
- we had in mind.
- Right? The genres have changed.
(His rock spirit is still sleeping
in this gentle morning.)
(Walking his hands back)
(Feeling refreshed)
(After his morning stretch,)
(he washes his face
with the headband on.)
- That's pretty powerful.
- He washes his face like an oldie.
He washed behind his ears too.
Right.
I feel so fresh.
(I feel so fresh.)
(Slapping)
- But doesn't that feel refreshing?
- Right.
- I feel like I must slap hard...
- Yes.
- for my skin to absorb the toner.
- Everyone does that.
My gosh.
It's over.
There must always be music.
(Captain Rock can't live
without music.)
It's "La Bamba."
(Humming)
(He turns on the lamp
while dancing.)
(Beeping)
(Sliding open)
(Heading to the kitchen
after securing the sunlight)
Your morning is really well-spent.
Yes. I'm a morning person.
- Really?
- I love spending my morning.
I thought he'd be a night owl.
(Having a blast in the morning)
(The sentimental rocker's morning
routine flows without interruption.)
Play the guitar, Rock Pup!
He's like the main character
in an American TV show.
I bet you toss trash
like you're playing basketball.
I bet you do that.
He also reminds me of Kevin
in "Home Alone."
When his mom isn't home.
(Whirring)
(Drip coffee)
You're making coffee?
I didn't learn it properly
at an academy or anything.
I've been making my own drip coffee
for over ten years.
Then he must be a real expert.
- Yes.
- He's been doing it for a decade.
I enjoy those coffee-making moments.
It feels like I'm spending
those moments only for myself.
There's no right answer in flavors.
I can change my coffee
based on my mood that day.
It's fun.
I'll give you
a coffee-related present next time.
Really?
(Thinking)
(He thinks for a moment
and then grabs something.)
The floral tea set is...
from my mother's house.
But it looks more stylish
because it's at your place.
- Right.
- It doesn't look like hers.
Coffee time.
My gosh.
(He sits at the table where
he turned on the light before.)
He looks so classy.
(Captain Rock has
quite the classy taste.)
That's a nice morning routine.
(Sipping)
(Hitting the spot)
(This is nice.)
(Enjoying a moment
while gazing into the sunlight)
Everything is so different,
but harmonizes so well.
Right. Without a good taste,
it would've looked so chaotic.
- Right.
- There's no sense of unity.
But strangely,
they blend in well together.
(A collage of his layered tastes)
(Let me see.)
What?
That's not a bass guitar.
I play the guitar too.
I write a lot of songs
with my acoustic guitar.
He's so cool.
(Humming)
(Pondering)
(He types something on his laptop
while mumbling something.)
"Send..."
- My gosh.
- He's writing the lyrics.
"I..."
(While basking in the warm sun,)
(he focuses on writing his song.)
"It's okay."
We're on different paths,
but in the same world
I'm definitely a morning person...
which isn't so common among rockers.
Here's why. I also write a column.
I'm a writer.
On top of that,
I also write lyrics and melodies.
There's something...
different about my writing
when bathed in the morning sun.
It's touched
by the morning moisture.
- What a lovely expression.
- Like the morning dew.
We're also part of nature.
The morning makes me feel like
I'm budding like plants.
My thoughts bloom
in the morning too.
So I try to embrace
this sense of light...
when I write my songs.
His expressions are quite poetic.
The most famous song
of Crying Nut is...
"Luxembourg."
("Luxembourg,"
lyrics and melody by Han Kyung Rok)
(The initial draft
of Kyung Rok's lyrics)
You have a notebook
with your lyrics.
"Deep in the Night."
(He also wrote the lyrics
and melody of "Deep in the Night.")
I've written...
a lot of lyrics
for other singers as well.
I wrote the lyrics...
for "Sweet Little Kitty"
by Cherry Filter.
- "Sweet Little Kitty" too?
- It was a huge hit.
No way.
- My gosh.
- It was a mega hit song.
No way. He still has notes
for the song. That's crazy.
That was the initial draft.
"Small dancing lights."
You didn't change the lyrics.
"Deep in the Night"
and "Sweet Little Kitty" used to...
bring in a lot of royalties.
Then Car the garden sang...
"Myeongdong Calling."
- "Myeongdong Calling."
(Car the garden's
sorrowful version...)
(of "Myeongdong Calling"
was beloved by the listeners.)
You're the original singer.
(But the original song belongs
to Crying Nut.)
No way.
A long time ago, I had
a part-time job in Myeong-dong.
- It was around Christmas.
- Myeong-dong.
It was snowing and cold.
But the couples looked so happy.
I wrote "Myeongdong Calling"
based on that experience.
- My gosh.
- From my memory of that day.
You're inspired
by every moment of your life.
(It looks like...)
(his daily life and inspiration
go hand in hand.)
- Rock and roll.
- He ends with "rock and roll."
Peace.
Hip-hop.
(Finding him cute)
(He finishes writing songs
in the morning on a good note.)
I ought to eat something.
(Opening his fridge)
Okay.
(Kimchi and delivery food
are in the fridge.)
(A simple fridge)
This is porridge.
(Grabbing his old delivery food)
(He also takes out
simple side dishes for the meal.)
(He's going into the kitchen?)
(Opening)
Those cups look so cute.
(Among many bowls,
he grabs the one he likes.)
(Transferring a desired amount
of porridge to the bowl)
(He opens up
the adjacent cabinet next.)
(Thinking)
You are moving them
on your own plate.
- Yes, I got the food delivered.
- Okay.
- Eating it in a pretty bowl...
- Right. I'd plate it too.
and plating it nicely
before I eat it...
make me feel like I'm loving myself.
- Like I'm cherishing myself.
- Right.
- This is nothing like...
- So...
what Kian84 expected to see.
- His house is so clean.
- This is great. I love it.
- I'm sorry, I'm too clean.
- Gosh, no.
- You're apologizing for that?
- You are...
(Plating a bit of the salad)
I get several dishes delivered.
Then I come up with
my own combination for my meals.
(He can't forget
about the porridge...)
(and the toast.)
- Kaya toast.
- Yes, it is.
(How did these dishes
end up together?)
It's like you're at a buffet.
(A shocking combination
of Kyung Rok's meal)
(Mixing)
(Blowing)
(He has a bite of the Korean dish,
the porridge, first.)
(It's hot.)
(Then he goes
after the Western-style salad.)
(Munching)
(Drinking the dongchimi juice
to finish his meal)
(Hitting the spot)
(I'm done with my meal.)
(Water running)
(He cleans up
right after his delicious meal.)
(Clearing his throat)
(Now that he's full,
he blasts the song he likes.)
(Dancing to the song, "60's Cardin")
There's a soundtrack
for everything you do.
There is.
He turned his life into a movie.
I'd like to be the main character
of my life if possible.
(Slicking it back)
- My gosh.
- Oh, my.
(Here comes Rocker Han Kyung Rok.)
You have several bandanas
in the same design.
I probably have 100 of them.
I probably have 100 bandanas.
I have them in different colors too.
(Wincing)
It's his signature style.
The moment I put on my bandana,
I become Captain Rock.
Should I say
it symbolizes freedom and romance?
Where do you buy your bandanas?
There are a lot of rare bandanas...
- at rest stops on expressways.
- Right!
- Right. I've seen them there.
- Aren't they good?
- It's on the head of a mannequin.
- Something like that.
- Right.
- Trot albums are right next to it.
- Yes.
You bought them there?
Yes, I did.
No way! I thought you bought them
at a hip store in Hongdae.
You might think they're all red.
- Right.
- But they're all different.
- Yes. I know.
- Right.
Some of them have
drawings of mountains.
- Right.
- Yes!
They sell bandanas
at the foot of Mount Seorak.
- Right. I buy them there too.
- Yes.
That's right.
(His bandana from a rest stop is
tightly fastened around his head.)
(Looking stylish
with a gold earring)
(With sunglasses,
he transforms into Captain Rock.)
Great.
(He sets out
after dressing up to the nines.)
(Revving it up)
(Captain Rock's red motorcycle
rolls down the road.)
This is the Han Kyung Rok we know.
He's so stylish.
(As he stylishly rides
the motorcycle...)
It's Hongdae. The smell of Seoul.
I'm here.
- It's a motorcycle shop.
- Yes.
Is Sung Hwan at the shop?
Hello.
I want to check the tire pressure.
Sometimes,
I can't start the engine in one go.
- Okay. Sure.
- Can you check on that too?
Thank you. I love you.
- Happy New Year.
(Excited)
He's so cute.
(He trots away after leaving
his motorcycle in the shop.)
The sun feels amazing.
(His mood is improved.)
(He casually walks
into the streets of Hongdae.)
- I haven't been there in ages.
- It's been so long for me too.
The perfect street for a stroll.
A lot has changed.
- A lot has changed.
- Right.
Hongdae is the hometown of my heart.
The time I spent in Hongdae
making music...
is longer than the time
I lived with my family.
It's much longer.
I go to Hongdae
more than three days a week...
to practice and perform at shows.
Even though
I don't spend a long time there,
the moment I arrive in Hongdae,
I'd tell myself,
"Hongdae even smells different."
I get this nostalgic vibe
when I visit.
A lot of my friends live
in every alley of Hongdae.
I can't help but love Hongdae.
I feel like
Hongdae has the best Seoul vibe.
I had something like...
longing for Hongdae.
- Of course.
- So,
when my friends and I reunited
after school break,
we asked each other,
"What did you do during the break?"
"I hung out in Hongdae."
It was something to brag about.
Yes. Hongdae represented Seoul.
A visit to Hongdae made you stylish.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Among friends in your hometown?
- Yes.
I went to Hongdae
and ate Jopok Tteokbokki.
- Jopok Tteokbokki.
- It's a must. There are branches.
- It's a part of the course.
- That's right.
- Ji Hyeon,
I should give you a Hongdae tour.
I should take you
to the nooks and crannies.
Let's be his guides.
Let's have a Hongdae tour.
- Hello.
- Happy New Year.
Which coffee beans are good today?
The ones from Rwanda are good.
The ones from Panama are unique.
- Panama?
- Yes.
- I'll buy a pack from Panama.
- Okay.
And recommend me something
that's nutty without acidity.
Among these options, I recommend
the ones from Nicaragua.
Nicara...
Hey, it's Nicara.
I'm sorry.
(Very funny)
- That tells us his age.
- Yes.
I also need a recommendation
on coffee I'll drink here.
I'll just have a hot Americano.
Do you want it to be acidic
as always?
- I want it to be acidic.
- Okay.
Did you enjoy
the Crying Nut concert?
My voice was gone the next day.
- From screaming?
- Everyone partied together.
- I'll show you to the inside.
- The inside.
(Rummaging)
- Sir.
- Yes?
It's a merchandise...
- for Crying Nut's 30th anniversary.
- Okay.
Take it as a souvenir. It's a gift.
- Thank you.
- I always enjoy your coffee.
Thank you.
- You should come sometime.
- Thirtieth anniversary.
A musician who can welcome
his 30th anniversary.
(Proud)
- Enjoy your coffee.
- Thank you.
(Sipping)
(My goodness.)
It thaws my body.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Happy New Year.
It's the clock tower.
(Happy)
(Singing)
(He enters a building as he hums.)
- Is it still there?
- That's right.
(He enters a building as he hums.)
- Hello.
- Just today,
- Okay.
- my flowers wilted.
- Right.
- I came to get new flowers.
- Did he go to a flower shop?
(He's a flower enthusiast who enjoys
his therapeutic time with flowers.)
- I...
- The flowers you want...
- Okay.
- are over here.
(Full of pretty flowers
of various shapes and colors)
Seriously, nothing is going
as I expected today.
It's like a fairy's day.
A fairy's day.
I think this one suits you well.
Gerbera is a nice choice too.
- As for gerbera,
- Okay.
I recently received it as a gift.
- It'll look nice with yellow roses.
- Okay.
- Yellow roses.
- He knows all the flowers.
Those purple flowers are nice too.
Yes. They're pretty.
- Complementary colors...
- Isn't this a common poppy?
It's an anemone.
- Anemone.
- Yes.
Don't anemones represent
one-sided love?
- "Even if you don't love me,"
- That's right.
- "I'll love you."
Do you know
the meaning of each flower?
I know it for a few flowers.
- It's perfect.
- Yes.
It's very pretty.
It's cold, so...
- Do you carry it in your coat?
- Let's go like this.
It's cold outside.
Bye. All right.
(He puts the flowers in his coat
so that they wouldn't be cold.)
It's cold.
(He navigates the streets of Hongdae
with ease.)
The streets are slippery.
(He walks diligently.)
Oh, my.
(He enters a building
in the alleys.)
What's this place?
Is anyone here?
(Hey!)
(Full of rock spirit)
(A rock-concept store
with charismatic mood)
I thought
your house would look like that.
- Seriously.
- That's right.
- I mean...
- You're full of prejudices.
That's right.
Ji Hyeon, it's like expecting
your place to be full of spangles.
That's right.
Is that it?
- Happy New Year.
Hey, why do you have flowers
on your chest?
I thought they might be cold.
- The flowers?
- Yes.
I bought a small gift...
because we haven't seen each other
in a while.
My goodness.
- Tiger.
- You shouldn't have.
Hey, Crying Nut welcomed...
- its 30th anniversary.
- Okay.
- Did you even write a letter?
- Yes.
You're close to all the owners
in the neighborhood.
They're my friends
Does Street Guns have any plans...
for a concert or an album?
We're still recording.
- Are you still recording?
- Yes.
- Are Cheol Su and all doing well?
- Cheol Su is getting married.
What?
- With whom?
- Dorothy.
- Dorothy?
- Yes.
- How nice. They'll get married.
- Those names...
- Can Cheol Su and Dorothy...
even get married?
- It's very...
- There are...
many international marriages.
In Hongdae, people use stage names.
(Please don't misunderstand.)
- It was nice seeing you.
- Keep on rocking.
We'll keep on rocking, for sure.
(He hits the streets again
after the third visit.)
Kyung Rok, you live
the life of a president.
He's the president of Hongdae.
I made a round
to see the faces I had missed.
How many numbers do you have
in your contact?
I think I have over 3,000.
Did you say 3,000?
Yes. My friends jokingly tell me...
to run for Mapo-gu's
district representative.
- You'll get the position.
- Seriously.
- You'll get many votes.
- Yes.
(Hongdae President continues
to make a round with ease.)
(What's this place?)
Hey.
- What's up?
- He's so popular.
- Happy New Year.
- Merry Christmas.
(Jebi Coffee House)
- It's Jebi Coffee House.
- Jebi Coffee House.
(When you enter
through the red iron door)
This is a place...
everyone in Hongdae drops by.
That's right.
It's a fun place
because the ceiling is open.
You can watch the performance
from the upper floor.
- Everyone looks down.
- That's right.
Jebi Coffee House is a place...
where the audience members
and artists who want to have...
their unique colors gather around.
It's like a hideout.
(The lineup of the performances
is written at the entrance.)
(IU, HYUKOH)
(A hideout that's visited
by various artists)
(Car the garden)
(Chang Ki Ha)
(The artists enjoy themselves
with the audience members here.)
(Still, isn't that good?)
What's this?
People who make an effort
to preserve...
the unique culture of Hongdae...
gather around in this place.
It's such a meaningful place.
What? Is that Ryoo Seung Bum?
He's a member
of Bulnabang Star Sausage Club,
- Cho Carlos.
- Bulnabang Star Sausage Club.
How do they come up
with these names?
These days, there's a band called
Cha Cha with the Cousins.
- That's right.
- Are they doing well?
Back in the day, they had
an Arabic-sounding name.
- Sultan of the Disco.
Where are they?
- As for them...
- They...
- One member of Nahzam Sue.
- Sultan of the Disco.
- Nahzam Sue?
- So...
Hongdae is a chaotic place.
It isn't anything bad.
So you need a wild name.
- I see.
- You should turn your weakness...
into your strength.
- How hip.
- Nice.
Hair Fibers Moomoo Fifty.
- Something like that.
- A band name?
- Hair Fibers Moomoo...
- Yes.
- Did you come up with my name?
(Happy)
(Cheering)
- No.
- Make some noise!
Adding "Hair fibers" doesn't suit
the Hongdae vibes.
"Soot black" is more fitting.
Soot Black Moomoo Bald Head!
Come on!
It's paradoxical.
- Soot Black Moomoo Bald Head.
- My goodness.
- Let's take a seat.
- Why is it so cold today?
- What are you doing now?
(Gosh, it's cold.)
Hey, have a drink. It's on me.
- That sounds good.
- What should we drink?
- Well,
- Espresso.
anything you want.
- Caffe latte.
- Okay.
- You have so many friends.
- I want the deep dark version.
You know all of them, right?
- They're always there.
- I see.
I brought something...
for the brothers.
- This will be useful for you.
- My goodness.
A warm mug.
- Thank you.
- A warm mug.
Last year...
Each gift is personalized.
- You began learning Japanese.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- You're so warm-hearted.
By the way,
- I'm preparing for Kyung Rok Day.
- Right.
Chang Hun made the poster
for the first Kyung Rok Day.
It was when Kyung Rok Day
was becoming big.
Some people might know this,
but Hongdae has
the three big holidays.
Halloween, Christmas Eve, and...
It's a bit embarrassing,
but the last one is Kyung Rok Day.
It's my birthday party that's named
after me, Han Kyung Rok.
(Birthday party
that's a holiday in Hongdae)
- That's grand.
- Yes.
Is that a birthday party?
Kyung Rok is incredible.
(One person's birthday
makes the entire Hongdae go wild.)
(At first, the birthday party
started at a chicken restaurant.)
(Kim Chang Wan)
- For years...
- In which year did it begin?
- Oh, my.
- It began in 2008.
- What?
- Cho Seung Woo?
- Cho Seung Woo came once.
(Then it became too big
for a chicken restaurant.)
(Thus, Kyung Rok Day began.)
(It has gone on for 18 years.)
Your birthday became so big.
- It's a festival.
- Yes.
I see that there's
a birthday celebration as well.
(People celebrate
Kyung Rok Day together.)
(He even won an award
at the Korean Music Awards...)
(for Kyung Rok Day.)
Is he like Kim Il Sung?
In North Korea,
they celebrate the Day of the Sun.
Crying Nut has many members.
Why is there only Kyung Rok Day?
I like to party the most.
I love partying with people.
I used to save up the money
I got for copyrights...
- for a few months.
- Okay.
- And on that day,
- You splurged.
I went, "It's on me!"
When people came to the event,
drinks and fried chicken...
- were on me.
- So...
- you practically began flexing.
- There was music too. That's right.
- You began the trend.
- Did you pay for everyone who came?
- I used to do that.
- He spent everything he earned.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- Afterward, it was out of my hands.
- Of course.
About 800 people showed up.
- How much was the total?
- And...
they drank one million
cubic centimeters of beer.
- One million cubic centimeters?
- Yes.
Was it Oktoberfest?
- It was something like that.
- One million cubic centimeters?
No way. That's unbelievable.
I realized, "I can't pay for this
no matter how successful I become."
- That's right.
- So eight years ago,
I began asking for sponsorships.
- It became a festival.
It became an event
of cultural exchanges.
- There must be guest singers.
- There are many guest singers.
- Who?
- Choi Baek Ho, Han Young-Ae...
And Glen Matlock of Sex Pistols
sent a video.
(The guest singers are
on another level.)
(Choi Baek Ho)
You can't even recruit them
for shows.
They performed for free.
Is that Han Young-Ae? Oh, my.
(Various artists participate
in the event.)
(MeloMance)
(The event took place online
during the pandemic.)
It's Do Hyun.
(Jannabi)
(The live broadcast
went on for 18 hours.)
The genres are diverse too.
I think your statue
will be erected in Hongdae later.
I'm pressed for time right now.
- I made drafts for the poster.
- I see.
- Oh, my.
- The 2026 Kyung Rok Day.
- It's dynamite. It's a draft.
- What is that?
Is that dynamite?
It's the horse dynamite.
- There's fire on the tail.
- It's the year of the horse.
- Let's see.
- Like this.
- It's very nice. I like the colors.
- It explodes.
- It's very nice.
- It's like a firework.
The drawing is cute.
- Like this.
- Youth.
Let's set off
the fireworks of romance.
- I see.
- The fireworks of romance...
You're doing whatever you want.
My draft...
- became this poster.
- I see.
While the work was rushed,
it has all the components.
(Draft, final work)
You should give the designer
a deep bow.
It's practically a new work.
So, that's the poster.
(That's what the poster looks like.)
Now, let's go over everyone's role.
- Eui Dong.
- Yes.
Eui Dong,
- you need to set up...
- Promote Kyung Rok Day.
the symbol of Kyung Rok Day,
flags of all nations.
- An important senior will come.
- Okay.
When that senior comes,
- please help with parking.
- Okay.
- Is he in charge of parking?
- Parking is intense in Hongdae.
- That's right.
- Please look after the senior.
Please film many short-form videos.
Chang Hun,
please share your ideas...
for the artistic aspects.
We need to promote the event.
It must be nice to have
many friends.
That's right.
When I plan something,
my friends gather around
and make it happen.
I think it's the Hongdae culture.
When is Kyung Rok Day?
- It'll be on February 19 and 20.
- It'll happen soon.
Hyun Moo, shall we have Moomoo Day?
Shall we have Moomoo Day?
- Let's do it.
- Can you draw a poster for it?
- In what month is your birthday?
- Let's party.
- My birthday is November 7.
- It isn't until much later.
We'll need a year to prepare.
A year?
- Moomoo Day.
- Prepare bread as finger food.
- I'll prepare...
- Bread is a good idea.
I'll prepare food.
Ji Hyeon, give
an opening performance.
I'll do that.
I'll make the poster.
When you have Moomoo Day,
invite Crying Nut.
That'll be incredible.
- I'll have the 50th birthday party.
- It'll be great.
What was my name?
Soot Black... What?
- Soot Black Moomoo Bald Head.
- I see.
- SMB.
I'll do a performance
as Soot Black Moomoo Bald Head.
I'll spend money.
- Moomoo Day will be fun.
- It'll be fun.
- Chang Hun, please do that.
- Okay.
I'll pester Hyun Woo
to do this and that.
Gosh, it's cold.
I'll pester Hyun Woo
to do this and that.
Gosh, it's cold.
BIBI.
- Hello.
- It's Hyeong Seo. It's BIBI.
- My goodness.
- BIBI.
- He's so well-connected.
- No way.
(The singer
behind the "Bam Yang Gang" craze)
(She has charisma
that sweeps the festivals.)
BIBI is my Hongdae junior.
(Singer BIBI)
- Thanks for coming when it's cold.
- Don't mention it.
Gosh, it's Kyung Rok's...
It's Crying Nut's merchandise.
- Crying Nut. Nut30.
- Nut30.
- She has merchandise too.
- She showed up in the merchandise.
- She came to the concert.
Have you been to the basement a lot?
I've been there,
- but I only drank.
- Of course.
That's the staircase to the basement
of Jebi Coffee House.
(At the bottom of the staircase
that's full of posters)
It isn't easy to get a table there.
- Really?
- It's full of people.
You can't go in there on weekends.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
Is Tiger JK doing well?
- Send him my regards.
- Okay. I did last time.
- We began around the same time.
- Yes.
We starred in
"Yoon Do Hyun's Love Letter" a lot.
Would she know the show?
(Being born in 1998, BIBI was
a child when the show aired.)
Even I don't remember much
of "Yoon Do Hyun's Love Letter."
I love Drunken Tiger's fourth album.
"Because I'm a Man."
I love the song titled "One Han."
I see. I don't really know
the CEO's songs.
- You don't need to know them.
- No.
I prefer Crying Nut.
Oh, my. Thank you.
He has a great artist in his agency.
I've been obsessed
with something recently.
With what?
- Crying Nut.
- Really?
- He looks happy.
- I do.
I had no interest in rock.
I just thought that it was cool.
I didn't go...
- I didn't have that reaction.
- You didn't like it that much.
And you were a middle-aged man
I always saw at the pub.
Anyone can see
that I'm a middle-aged man.
Yes. But when you took the stage,
you totally devoured it.
- I did?
- You commanded the world.
I loved it so much.
- I seemed different.
- Yes.
(He didn't seem like
the man she saw every day.)
"That's youth."
(Startled)
I'm so thankful...
- you felt that.
- Yes.
I felt nostalgic for the things...
I had never experienced.
- It was like, "Things were good."
- Yes.
His eyes are sparkling.
It was insane.
When I see something great,
I want to turn it into my work.
So I thought, "What should I do?"
"How can I work with Kyung Rok?"
Then I ran into you in a pub.
So I decided to send you a highball.
(She plucked up the courage
and sent him a highball.)
- It was an honor. Seriously.
- So...
(Work with me.)
(You?)
(You're the best!)
You're something else.
- She's much younger.
- That's right.
We became close in no time.
Before I forget, I prepared...
- a small gift.
- A gift again?
- Nice.
- Kyung Rok, you go around...
- giving gifts.
- Seriously.
You should ride Rudolph,
not a motorcycle.
- Santa Claus.
- He really is Santa Claus.
Hongdae's Santa Claus.
- I'll open it.
- Okay.
They're my favorite accessories.
Is it a bracelet?
I brought the ones I used.
I bought it...
from a street stall.
It isn't expensive.
- It's like a pirate's item.
- Yes.
- It's like a musical item.
(The pirate's mark is a key point.)
- It's romantic.
- You know,
I'm going crazy right now.
Do you know what
my favorite Crying Nut song is?
"The Pirate’s Path."
- That necklace is fitting.
- It's so cool.
- It's fitting.
- That's right.
- You got the telepathic message.
- I know.
(Cheering)
- Look at this.
- You like it.
I love it. It's insane.
There's something else.
Is there something else?
I thought it'd be nice
to give you a classic.
She likes books.
- It's really fun.
- Is it fun?
- It's fun.
- On the flyleaf...
(She spots something.)
(The page is full
of the handwritten message.)
- What kind of a book is it?
- Classics always survive.
That's right. They never die.
- Let's become the classics.
- Okay.
It's such a cool saying.
It's a cool saying.
I have so many worries
about Kyung Rok Day.
- I wanted to ask you something.
- Okay.
Why don't you do
a collaborative performance...
with Crying Nut?
If we do that...
She feels honored as a fan.
It'll be a good opportunity.
I love the idea.
BIBI and Crying Nut.
(Oh, my!)
It's a unique combination.
Sing a rock version
of "Bam Yang Gang."
Red bean jelly with chestnut
Sing it like that.
The sweetest snack
It'll be interesting.
That's right. Red bean jelly
can be the drinking snack.
- It'll be nice.
- It's a good idea.
(End of the meeting)
- It'll be nice.
- Kyung Rok!
Hey, Tigers!
Gosh, you're here.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- They're Far East Asian Tigers.
- Far East Asian Tigers.
- Why don't we go and say hello?
- Sure.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
The hottest indie rockstars
in Hongdae!
- You've been doing well, right?
- Of course.
Far East Asian Tigers?
- I'll introduce you to someone.
- They're hot these days.
Okay.
I'll introduce you to someone.
- This is BIBI. Hyeong Seo.
- Hello.
- And...
- this is Far East Asian Tigers.
- Right.
You know them, right?
We'll be performing together
on Kyung Rok Day.
It's an honor.
I wish you guys would
greet each other from now on.
- Right.
- That sounds great.
So that is how artists get together.
When I'm in Jebi Coffee House,
I meet a lot of bands that visit.
It feels like a salon of the past.
- Salon! Exactly.
- Right?
It's like a place
for Romantic painters of France.
- It has that feel.
- Right.
- Artists meet so naturally.
New ideas could be created
through those encounters.
- It's a salon.
(Hongdae salon)
- Well, let's eat together sometime.
- Right.
I'll see you next time.
- Bye!
I'll mascot you.
- "Mascot?"
- Yes.
(He says goodbye to BIBI as well.)
Can the Soot Black Moomoo
Bald Head's show...
- be done in Jebi Coffee House?
- Do you have something prepared?
I have to hold the Bald Show soon.
Do this and shake off
your hair powder.
Like this?
People can see you from the top.
The ceiling is open.
When the lights are on from there,
it will shine very brightly.
That's when I'll spin my head.
(A fantastic performance
is expected.)
- Get back safely.
- Happy New Year.
(His bike has finally been fixed.)
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
- The sun has set already.
You must feel lonely
when you head back home.
Right.
That's how it would feel
after being in a loud place.
Right.
(Along with his favorite bike
that feels a lot smoother,)
(Kyung Rok heads back home.)
He has flowers by his chest.
The petals fall off if I carry them
with the handle of the motorcycle.
- You can't do that.
- Right. You can't do that.
(He returns home
after the sun is down.)
(Letting out a breath)
Gosh.
(Placing down)
(Letting out a breath)
(He had the rock spirit
worn around his neck.)
(He puts it back
after folding it nicely.)
The moment you take off
your bandana at home,
- you feel like a different person.
- Right.
Right? The off button?
Right. The off button.
(Switching on)
(He starts turning on the lights
around the house.)
(Unlike the bright day
filled with natural light,)
Done.
(the night in Kyung Rok's house
has become much calmer.)
Today's flowers.
(He heads to the kitchen with the
flowers he bought during the day.)
(Being careful)
Gosh.
They must've felt cold.
(Turning around)
(I should prune them.)
(Kyung Rok carefully prunes
the flowers...)
(he brought preciously.)
- He's very romantic.
- Right.
(The flower vases were put together
very quickly.)
(Placing down carefully)
(He places them
where he wanted to place them.)
(Fiddling)
(He opens the coffee beans
he bought today.)
- Coffee?
- Coffee!
(Sniffing)
(Yes. This is it.)
(He puts them into
the glass jars nicely...)
(and stores them in the cupboard.)
(He gets the blanket that has
dried up nicely in the sun.)
- It must've dried up nicely.
- Right.
(He gets the blanket that has
dried up nicely in the sun.)
(He opens the fridge.)
(Let's see.)
(Taking out a bunch of things)
(He heads to the kitchen with a lot
of things to prepare for dinner.)
(Thinking)
(He chooses a cup that he likes...)
(and adds in scorched rice.)
- Scorched rice?
- I crave some at night.
Since I won't be having a lot,
I use a cup.
It's bad to have a heavy meal
at night.
(He craves scorched rice at night
for a light meal.)
(As he spent a busy day,)
(he quickly prepares his dinner.)
(Shall I eat now?)
(His dinner...)
He orders food.
(looks a lot like his breakfast.)
(Mixing)
(He takes a bite
of the warm porridge first.)
(Chewing)
(Without any music playing,)
(the place is silent.)
It's really quiet.
- He became a different person.
- Right.
When I come back home,
it feels like
my house comforts me with a hug.
I tend to keep quiet...
and let myself recharge.
(Lifting)
(The scorched rice
has been soaked just right.)
(Slurping)
(Letting out a breath)
(Just the sound of his spoon
and cup clashing can be heard.)
(Wiping)
After that...
(It was loud...)
(throughout the whole day.)
(The night deepens...)
(and I am alone.)
(It still doesn't...)
(feel so bad.)
When I was young,
there was no night or day.
I loved hanging out with friends
so much.
I drank during the day.
I drank for several days straight.
I even slept on the streets.
I freely enjoyed my life.
(The times I was carefree)
Now that those times have passed,
I feel like I need some time...
to talk with myself.
That is why
the time I spend alone...
has become a lot more precious.
I started enjoying
decorating the house...
and cleaning up the house.
I started working out
and taking care of myself.
(I am solely focused on myself now.)
I want to perform after writing
a song about my new self.
Of course,
"Speed Up Losers" is great,
but I want to sing about
my current emotions...
and this current generation.
I also want to be jumping around.
I don't want to look all mature
as a musician of 30 years.
I want to jump around...
- That's touching.
- as an active musician.
I don't want to fall behind
the musicians of this generation...
when it comes to energy.
I want to enjoy performing with them
as colleagues.
I want to give my energy
to the audience.
I want to make everyone jump.
I'm always progressing.
(Han Kyung Rock...)
(is still progressing.)
- Gosh!
- That was great.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- The ending spoke right at me.
- Right. It was so touching.
- Right.
Right.
How was it for you?
You've been in Hongdae
for a while as well.
It really...
reminded me
of the times I was young.
I felt the emotions
that I loved and missed.
It was an admirable life.
You looked like an artist
who is devoted to the audience.
I witnessed the moments
of a fool for music.
A fool for music
is such a pleasant thing to hear.
I don't want myself
to become too clever.
- A fool for music.
- You sound like a poet.
- Gosh.
- That was so nice.
Gosh.
While seeing you today,
I thought that you looked
much younger than your age.
But I think your eyes
look the youngest.
You have the eyes of a young man.
Actually, I was reminded of Picasso.
- Picasso?
- Picasso once said this.
"It took me four years
to draw like Raphael,"
"but it took me my whole life
to draw like a child."
- Right.
- It's a really hard thing to do.
It's hard for us
to draw like a child...
because we adults know so much
and have experienced many things.
But I felt that through your eyes.
You have a sense of innocence
of a child.
That was why I thought
you never aged.
It was a day
that motivated me a lot.
That's such a great thing to hear.
It feels like we're in Hongdae
at 3am.
Gosh, this feels great.
All of us are drunk.
More peaches, please.
(The night in Hongdae never ends.)
(I Live Alone)
(Heave-Ho! Winter Survival)
(One, two)
- What? Running?
- Running?
Gosh!
I don't think it's a Fun Run,
judging by the speed.
It's not a Fun Run.
You could die during a Fun Run
at that speed.
I gained around 5kg
compared to the summer.
- Right now?
- Yes.
You look fine.
Since he's tall,
you can't tell if he gained 5kg.
My body felt a lot heavier.
That was why I decided
to lose some weight.
(He breathlessly runs somewhere.)
(Seoul Botanic Park)
- What?
- It's Seoul Botanic Park.
The Botanic Culture Center.
(He heads to the ticket booth
right away.)
I've been there a couple of times.
- You went there?
- I went with my friends.
- Really?
- The Botanic Park?
That's a sound place to visit
with your friends.
I thought the Botanic Park
was a place for elders.
- It's really nice there.
- Right.
Do you like plants?
I don't like them too much.
Is that so? What a bummer.
I'm the only one
who loves plants here.
I also love plants.
- Right.
- I have hydroponic plants.
- Hydroponic plants?
- They're easy to take care of.
- I'll teach you later.
- Hydroponic plants.
I have 100 times more
of what you 2 have combined.
I have 100 times more.
I've never been to the Botanic Park.
Don't just be working out.
Visit those places as well.
Right. He started out with running,
so I thought it was...
- something I would love.
- No.
- No!
- It ended right away.
I feel slightly disappointed.
- You should've run a bit more.
- You look like a killer right now.
- Really?
- Right.
- Okay.
- There are a lot of men here.
- I should hold it in.
- You look like a gunman.
- A ticket for 1 adult, please.
- Right. It's 5 dollars.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
The tickets are cheap.
- Right.
- The Botanic Park is really nice.
Place the QR code here.
Thank you.
(Conservatory Entrance)
(He heads straight into
the Conservatory.)
It must feel warm in there
during the winter.
(Right into the warm Conservatory!)
(Right after entering, he heads
straight into the Conservatory.)
(Amazed)
(A place full of green
even during the winter)
It's really nice.
- It's like an amusement park.
- Right.
This is so fascinating.
I didn't know there was
a place like this in Seoul.
(The warm sunlight seeps in.)
It's warm inside.
(The flowers show off
their bright colors.)
(This place even feels mystical.)
It really feels mystical.
It looks great.
My hands and feet are always cold.
I feel cold easily...
and catch colds often.
Since I'm a singer,
- catching a cold...
- That would be critical.
- would make me lose all of my gigs.
- Right.
I try my best
to avoid catching colds.
I hate being cold.
I hate winter so much.
I found out that the Botanic Park...
was the warmest place
during the winter.
I wondered how warm it could be...
and decided to pay a visit.
My immune system
got weakened last year...
and caught colds
three times straight.
- Gosh.
I've developed this obsession
of not wanting to catch a cold.
Isn't it worse since singers
are sensitive about their throats?
- What about you, Dowoon?
- I don't sing.
(I don't sing.)
I saw you sing a lot.
That was just
for a special occasion.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
How do you take care of your throat?
- It's a sensitive matter.
- As for me,
when I feel like
I'm about to catch a cold...
(How does the senior with 19 years
of experience take care of himself?)
I get up early...
and make myself sweat a lot
through a workout.
- That's how you catch a cold.
- Gosh.
(That's how you catch a cold.)
- That gets rid of the cold.
- You have to rest your body.
Have you ever missed a performance
due to a cold?
That has never happened to me.
- Really?
- Not even once.
I don't remember myself
catching a cold recently.
One's immune system
is really important.
The immune system
keeps you safe from colds.
I think good sleep is important.
- Right.
- Good sleep leads to that.
It's great in here.
(Breathing in)
(Breathing out)
It must feel refreshing to the nose.
You keep trying to smell things
in there.
Right.
It was nice.
It felt really warm and cozy.
It was damp and smelled really nice.
- The humidity is at 86 percent?
- Gosh.
Tropical plants can only live
in those conditions.
That's perfect for me.
Gosh.
It feels like
"Adventures of Sinbad."
(It feels like
"Adventures of Sinbad.")
(When you walk through
the thick forest...)
Gosh.
This is fascinating.
A palm tree is this big.
(He finds a huge baobab.)
- What?
- There's a baobab.
There's a baobab there?
(Surprised)
- Did you see them in Africa?
- I saw the ones there.
The big ones are over 30m tall.
(The giant trees that usually grow
in tropical climates)
They're unbelievably tall.
I heard they live
for 2,000 years to 5,000 years.
They have that there as well?
(Amazed)
(Breathing out)
(Breathing in)
- Gosh.
(What was that?)
- I just wanted to smell the place.
- I thought it was Jim Carrey.
(I thought it was Jim Carrey.)
Must you smell the place
with that kind of face?
I get charged with freshness
by doing that.
- Right.
(The face of wanting to feel
the most freshness)
(He spots a pretty flower.)
(Satisfied)
(He charges himself up again.)
You look like a Disney character.
(You look like a Disney character.)
Doesn't he look like a prince?
- Right.
Gosh, it's so nice.
(Breathing out)
(The prince breathes
quite enthusiastically.)
(He goes around
and charges himself with freshness.)
(This is it.)
Check out his face.
You became a silly little boy
at the Botanic Park.
- I wanted to feel the place.
- I've never seen you...
make faces like that before.
(What does this smell like?)
(He spreads out his legs
all of a sudden.)
He's really into this.
That's how they must be felt.
- I always do that as well.
- Right.
- Right into the nose.
They're just like each other.
(Rubbing)
- He really enjoys smelling them.
- He loves it there.
He's enjoying himself.
These ones are funny.
They really are.
(He's drenched in sweat.)
- He's drenched in sweat.
- Right.
Gosh, why is it so hot in here?
(It's too hot for me.)
(He heads outside
while feeling satisfied.)
Interesting.
(He puts on his jacket
right after going outside.)
Let's call a taxi.
(He calls a taxi
and heads somewhere.)
Where are you going now?
(Sighing)
(I feel drowsy.)
Why are you making so many faces?
You make more faces than a comedian.
(His facial expressions
were especially dynamic today.)
(Rolling his eyes)
I'm not sure why I was like that.
(He feels sleepy in the warm car.)
(Yawning)
Gosh, my mouth is so big.
(His yawn has spread to him.)
Warm winter.
(Warm winter)
Warm.
(Warm)
I want a warm winter
- Warm in winter
- He has lost himself.
I must've gotten drunk
by the plants.
Gosh.
(He arrives somewhere
while humming.)
Deungchon-ro?
(Walking)
(Impressed)
Why are there so many people?
What is this place?
I did some research...
and there was
a market around my area...
that sells different things.
To feel warm during the winter,
I went to buy cozy pajamas.
(Mokdong Kkaebi Market)
Kkaebi Market?
(It's filled with clothes that
help us stay warm during winter.)
(Warm steam)
Fishcakes.
Fishcakes taste the best
during the winter.
(It's loaded
with winter snacks as well.)
(The market is packed
even in the cold weather.)
There are so many people.
Blueberries.
(Trying to rhyme)
Should I get pajamas?
That seems to be in trend
these days.
It's pretty.
(It's to my liking.)
(Carefully scanning)
This seems nice.
Pants? Pajama pants?
(Grabbing a pair
of fleece-lined pants)
Excuse me.
Do I pay for
the things from upstairs here?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Aren't you Park Ji Hyeon?
- Oh, hello.
I'm in the 49th batch
of Mokpo Technical High School.
- I'm in the 49th batch.
- What does he mean?
- Pardon?
- Mokpo Technical High School.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He's your senior?
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
(He met his high school senior
by chance in Seoul.)
- He's your senior.
- Really?
It's nice to meet you.
- He recognized me right away.
- My goodness.
It's always nice seeing someone
from my hometown in Seoul.
Right. I agree.
- You're in the 49th batch?
- Yes.
- I'm in the 80-something batch.
- You're handsome!
That's so cool.
Thank you.
I studied architecture.
Oh, my! What is this?
These are my initials.
What? Initials?
- It's P...
- PJH?
- You're right.
- You must get that.
Park Ji Hyeon. This is so...
It's fate.
My goodness.
I should get this.
You're absorbed in that brand.
PJH.
The coincidences are unreal.
Right. You met the senior and
found clothes with your initials.
I'm splurging.
I'll take these three.
Just pay for these two.
I'll give you one as a gift.
- No, it's all right.
- No, still, I want to.
- It's okay.
- Come on. It's cheap.
- Still...
- Just give me 20 dollars.
- Sure. Here you go.
- Thank you.
A senior who takes care...
- of his junior.
- Thank you for this.
Oh, my. He came out.
He's here.
Hello.
- Everyone's gone wild.
- Goodness. Take a photo with me.
Let's go, people from Mokpo!
Let's go!
- Hey, he's my son.
- Let's go!
- Quick. Take a photo with him.
- Stay healthy, son.
The prince of markets.
- Goodness.
- Thank you.
Yes. I've really wanted to see you.
- Goodness.
Everyone's gone wild.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
(Smiling)
There's metrics to measure
a trot singer's success.
You have to see if you can
walk through the market...
in peace or not.
It's always hard for me.
(Exploding with confidence)
(This is it.)
You need that kind of confidence.
Goodness, I knew it. PJH!
- PJH!
- PJH.
JYP is old news. It's PJH's era.
PJH!
(Dizzy)
Seriously, though.
I've never seen Ji Hyeon like this.
- I know.
- Humility isn't always a virtue.
Exactly.
The best initials next to JYP.
(You've got this, PJH.)
It's always hard for me.
Thank you.
I won the Popularity Award.
(It's me.
I won the Popularity Award.)
He became more easygoing.
(Park Ji Hyeon, the winner
of the Popularity Award...)
(from the 2025 MBC
Entertainment Awards)
- Yes, I won the award.
- Gosh, PJH.
(Thank you so much. Seriously...)
Many started liking me since.
They said I was handsome.
- "They said I was handsome."
I'll work even harder,
so that next time I go to a market,
I wouldn't be able
to walk through it easily.
(Impressed)
Ji Hyeon doesn't need to bring
his wallet to a market,
given his popularity, right?
- I know.
- He'd have carp bread...
in his mouth when he just walks by.
(Going overboard)
Your moment has come.
It's all thanks
to the Popularity Award.
- You're right.
- Of course.
Here he is.
- Hello.
- It's Ji Hyeon.
Hello.
- It's Park Ji Hyeon.
- They really go wild.
Gosh, your popularity is no joke.
Gosh, that looks good.
I should have one of those.
- Hello.
- Park Ji Hyeon.
Thank you.
- Hello.
- Are you having fish cakes?
Yes.
- I couldn't walk past that.
- It looks good.
Goodness.
It looks good.
I like the curly type better.
- That's the most delicious.
- Yes.
"It Melts" is my favorite song.
(Ji Hyeon's song)
Really?
(Singing right away)
Thank you.
(You know it,
but you act like you don't)
Thank you.
(Impressed)
(Tasting the fish cake,
feeling grateful)
Goodness.
(Exclaiming)
- Hello.
- You can't enjoy it in peace.
- I'm a fan.
- Sure.
(Taking a photo with a fan
right away even while eating)
- You're so easygoing.
- Thank you.
(Showing a V-sign)
(After a mini fan meet-and-greet
in front of a snack bar)
Which strawberries are good?
Have this one. It's really good.
- I'll take one.
- Sure.
It's cute.
(He also got warm bed socks.)
(Grabbing a fuzzy vest this time)
I have one of those at home too.
Fuzzy vests are really popular
these days.
You know it became really popular
in other countries, right?
- Right. In other countries...
- Really?
Yes, they found it really pretty
after watching it in a K-drama.
No wonder. Every shop
displayed vests like those.
Foreigners buy those a lot.
- You haven't bought it, have you?
- I have.
(You don't even have to mention it.)
- Following the trend?
- I wasn't sharing...
so they could sell those more.
The trend could end
if people find out I bought it.
- You shouldn't end that trend.
- I shouldn't.
Also, it doesn't feel like
you're acting out with that.
- It makes you feel good.
- Of course.
- DCCs act out a lot.
- Right.
- DCCs are loud.
- It's not humble.
- Yes.
It feels like it's showing off.
- You need to go through a lot...
- It's arrogant.
before gaining all that popularity.
- Thank you.
(Finishing shopping with
winter gear)
(Ji Hyeon came back home
with his hands full.)
(Bringing a bunch in)
I got so much stuff.
(Turning on water
after putting his stuff down)
It's so realistic.
He always hangs his laundry there.
(Collecting the laundry
while he's at it)
(He takes care of his throat first
as usual.)
How many do you have?
I happened to collect them,
so I have five.
It's understandable.
Your throat
must be really sensitive.
Yes.
(Taking his socks off)
(Throwing)
As expected.
It's like I'm watching myself.
(Throwing them on the floor)
(Grabbing the new socks he got)
It's cute.
(You must wear the new ones
right away.)
With bed socks,
bold ones are better.
- I know.
- Right.
- Blue or red ones.
- Exactly.
- Or pink.
- The colors you can't wear outside.
(Sliding)
Right. You tend to do that
with bed socks.
- Exactly.
- Right?
(Thinking)
(Ji Hyeon suddenly cleans up
the coffee table.)
(He even brings a chair.)
(Lifting)
(Is it all set?)
Wait. Gloves?
Is he fixing something?
(Going up with no hesitating)
- Changing the light bulb?
- Is he changing the light bulb?
(Removing the cover
without hesitation)
He looks like an expert.
Gosh, because he's tall...
(He switches off the breaker
for safety.)
The lights seemed to be
working just fine.
Right. They looked fine.
(Beeping)
Who is it?
(Suddenly, someone has come
to Ji Hyeon's place.)
(Someone comes in
by opening the door themselves.)
You're here.
Why is it so dark in here?
- Because...
- Because of the light bulbs?
He's the friend I rely on the most.
He's Kang Jae Soo.
I first met him
when I went on "Mister Trot."
He told me he lived
in the same neighborhood,
so we sometimes ate out together.
That's how we became close.
(They've become even closer.)
He knows the passcode
to your place too?
Yes. He's the only friend
who knows the passcode to my house.
You guys must be really close.
Jae Soo always carries around
a toolbox in his car.
Jae Soo.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing. I'm at home.
Could you come over for a second?
- Why?
- Help me with something.
What? You brought the whole thing?
Jae Soo is extremely talented...
in architecture.
- Really?
- Yes.
He also got an architectural
engineering licence...
in the shortest possible way.
Oh, my.
He also majored architecture
in college.
I knew it. The toolbox he carried...
seemed like an expert's.
- It didn't look domestic.
- Right.
Hold on. Let me open it first.
I don't know how it looks.
Go ahead.
(Rattling)
What does he want to do?
How much of it does he want to fix?
What do you want to do with that?
You want to remove it
and install a remote control?
- Yes.
- What?
So I can turn it on and off
while I'm lying.
Because it's cold in winter,
you don't want to stay
under the blanket.
So that I don't need to walk
to switch off the lights,
he and I'd install a remote control
on the ceiling...
and change the bulb to a warmer one.
My house looks a bit cold,
so I wanted to make it look warm.
(He asked for help from
the architecture genius friend.)
Like this. Hold it.
Let's see. From here...
I think I need to connect it
to power first.
You just need to install this
on the inside?
- Then it gets connected?
- Yes.
(Okay, I got it.)
Do you have a wire cutter?
I have almost everything.
(Jae Soo is indeed great.)
- There's one, right?
- Yes.
(Glancing)
Give it to me.
Gosh, he's so cool.
(He's not hesitant
as he's a genius.)
I'll cut it for you.
- Hey, punk.
- It must not be easy.
Even men's hearts throb
when we see it.
(Skillful)
(When the architecture genius friend
hands it over...)
Hey, you're good too.
- I know.
- I used to install ACs too.
Oh, right.
That's why Ji Hyeon is good.
(The collaboration of
an architecture genius...)
(and a genius
from Mokpo Technical High School)
(Wiping)
Why is it so hot here?
What's the temperature?
Why am I sweating so much?
You should lower the temperature.
No, I can't catch a cold.
Hey, that's too hot.
I've never seen anyone
who keeps a room hotter than mine.
Gosh, 30°C?
I keep mine at 26°C.
- It's at 26°C.
- Mine's at 23 or 24°C.
How much do you pay
for the heating bill?
- The heating bill...
- It must cost a lot.
I pay about 100 dollars more
than when I don't turn it on.
- Actually, I can spend that much.
- That's not too bad.
You've made it.
Of course.
I even got the Popularity Award.
Have a warm year-end.
It's scary what
the Popularity Award can do.
I can afford it.
(I'm warm thanks to that.)
Catching a cold
isn't a problem here.
(Even with the Popularity Award,
keeping it at 30°C is a bit...)
No! Don't lower it.
- It's hot. No, I mean, it's cold.
- Gosh, it's hot.
You said it's hot
without even realizing.
Look at you sweating.
It's nice to sweat and all.
People need to sweat.
(It melts)
And then...
Even the song says, "It melts."
Stick it in and...
(He's about to melt
as it's as hot as 30°C.)
It's done once I put it back.
(Ready to connect)
Let's give it a try.
All right. Let's put it back.
(Stepping)
I'll carry it for you.
Put it back in.
- Here.
- Yes!
I wouldn't have been able
to do it without you.
This is kind of hard to do it
by yourself...
because someone needs to hold it
when I put it back in.
- You're right.
- You need two people for it.
That's right.
(Exhaling)
This is it.
(Turning on the light again
to check)
(Pressing the remote control)
(He succeeded in connecting it
in one go.)
- Gosh.
- It works.
- It's the best.
- It's connected.
I told you it'd work.
- It was bound to work.
- Right.
They can be turned on
on different levels now. Look.
One, two.
I can turn it off at once
if I want to.
Gosh, it's so convenient.
It's funny, right?
- It's nice.
- Yes.
(Now, I can stay under my blanket.)
- So, Jae Soo,
- Yes?
I want to change it
to a yellow bulb.
A yellow bulb? Which one?
Look. I bought this.
Okay.
Cover... Oh, you want to
put a film over it?
With cellophane?
Really?
Isn't it better to leave it
and get a floor lamp instead?
There are times
when you need the white light bulb.
You can put it on and off.
Then you have to call Jae Soo again.
- Call Jae Soo again?
- No.
Why do you make it so inconvenient?
- Everyone has their lifestyle.
- Right.
- I'll stick this on that.
- Let's try putting it on.
- To see the color?
- Yes.
I'll turn on the light
for a second, then.
(Lights on)
- All right. Good.
- Is it okay?
(All right. It's warm and nice.)
Now, we need to stick that here.
- They're in different colors.
- They're all yellow.
Don't they need to be
in the same color?
They're all in different colors.
All right.
(Is this right?)
(Tearing the yellow cellophane)
All right.
(Sticking it on the cover
right away)
(Jae Soo follows
and does what Ji Hyeon wants.)
Jae Soo is sweating profusely.
How nice of him.
If you make lights like this...
This is practically a sauna.
It's nice.
During winter, people like us...
can't get a cold.
You said that for the 150th time.
Got it.
Oh, like that?
You're not covering the whole thing?
Yes, the color turned out well.
I can't wait to see the color.
(I hope this is going well.)
(Dripping)
I'll turn on the light.
(Smiling)
- Gosh.
- It's not bad.
It looks like
a modern piece of artwork.
It's modern art.
It's clearly different as this
is a group of artists.
- The way you think.
- Of course.
(The house looked cold.)
It looks like the lighting
of a select shop.
It's warm, right?
Nice, right?
(Sure. It's really warm.)
It's warm.
I got you a gift.
- Yes?
- Would you like to try it on?
(It's warm already.
What else should I put on?)
To keep you warm
without catching a cold...
Oh, the things he got
from the market earlier?
Are we wearing matching items?
Yes, they're matching.
Then I'll take the black one.
- Your fan club's color is white.
- Oh, okay.
Isn't this yellow?
It's white.
It's because of the lighting.
Because of the lighting.
I'll go get changed.
(Meanwhile,
Jae Soo puts on socks first.)
I should take off my hoodie.
Jae Soo must be really hot.
- Here we go, Jae Soo.
- Isn't this too much?
Why?
He's wearing fleece-lined pants
when it's already hot?
It's nice and warm.
You have to keep warm this winter.
- You shouldn't catch a cold.
- I think it's a bit small.
You shouldn't catch a cold
if you want to sing.
It's a project to spend winter well.
He's so kind.
It looks good on you.
Why do the teddy bears
look so pitiful?
Isn't it a life vest?
It's so...
Wear it when you're home,
so you can stay warm.
Oh, also... I...
- I need to...
- Yes?
The coffee table...
You have a drill, right?
(Taking it out)
- Do you know that?
- Which one?
A Shin-chan table?
- A Shin-chan table?
- Yes.
What's a Shin-chan table?
So you cover the table
with a blanket.
And you keep your legs warm inside.
Oh, a kotatsu?
- Oh, kotatsu?
- Kotatsu.
Ja Yeon has that at home.
That one.
(A Japanese-style heated table)
You must hate being cold.
Japan has a table like that...
because
they don't have floor heating.
- That's true.
- The air is cold, so...
Actually,
why set up a table like that...
in a house with floor heating
at over 30°C?
- Why would you even have that?
- That's...
- Actually, you don't need it.
- Is that so?
I bet it's even hotter than
the sauna you and Dowoon went to.
I bet so.
I'm using it really well.
Otherwise, should I put charcoal
on the inside for you?
(Top-notch heating)
Yes, put charcoal under the table
for him.
It'd be better to put charcoal in.
(You can also call me
when you need to.)
(Whirring)
(The architecture genius
performs again for his friend.)
It's around here, right?
(Skillfully disassembling
and assembling it)
Oh, like that?
Oh, you're putting it on top?
It fits.
(Just trust me.)
He must've wanted to
take off that vest.
It must've been really hot.
I didn't know
he was struggling that much.
His bangs are all wet.
I know.
He kept it on for me.
(Sweating profusely)
Gosh, look at him sweating.
(Crying)
- Done.
- Yes, we did it.
(Excited)
Yes, this is it.
(Feeling proud)
- Here. Look.
- Yes, from here...
- Look.
- Okay.
I'd sit here like this.
While sitting...
You'd be lazy to go
and turn off the light.
I can turn it off like this.
(I can turn it off like this.)
- You look so happy.
- I can turn it off like this.
(The living room
that looked cold...)
(became much warmer
with the heated table.)
(The plain ceiling light...)
(got its own vibe
like that of a select shop's.)
(You can even turn it off
with a remote control.)
(Lastly,
with the current humidity...)
Gosh, it must be really hot.
(Instead of shabby sweats,)
(put on fuzzy vests, pajama pants,
and bed socks!)
(An impeccable TPO to spend winter)
Gosh, it's pretty.
Dowoon, thank you so much.
It's really pretty. I'm serious.
Ji Hyeon, why don't you change
the light bulbs for Dowoon's place?
(Flustered)
- Do you want him to change it?
- Well, I...
You saw his house.
It's really clean.
Dowoon's place looks like
a house created by AI.
- That's right. It's too spotless.
- It's too spotless.
I respect everyone's preferences.
You liar.
You said it was pretty...
- "It's pretty."
- because it wasn't your house.
I mean...
(Hitting the nail on the head)
Because it wasn't his house,
he went, "It's pretty!"
"It's really pretty."
- You should tell him honestly.
- That's right.
- It's not my style, but...
- Oh, it's not your style.
It's really pretty.
It's like mid-century modern style.
(Mid-century modern style)
If you need, I'll go
decorate your house right away.
Sure. I'd love that.
I can turn it on like this.
It's nice. By the way,
it's a bit cold here, right?
How can it be cold? It's 30°C.
- Actually, it should be...
- Yes?
heated underneath.
(Heated?)
(Ji Hyeon's heated table
doesn't have heater yet.)
(Bringing a bunch of hand warmers)
- Hand warmers?
- You're using hand warmers?
He must be crazy. This is...
It'll be really warm.
He's sweating so much though.
What on earth is he doing?
Look at Jae Soo's bangs.
Then you don't wash with warm water.
(Putting the hand warmers underneath
without seeing Jae Soo's bangs)
(He's let it all go.)
(Staring)
Hold on.
What are you going to do?
It looks like
his eyes are out of focus.
What are you going to do?
I'll make hotteok.
Order him
cold Pyongyang naengmyeon, will you?
He's dying from heat.
What hotteok? He's dying from heat.
It must be a lot of work.
You have to fry it too.
(Jae Soo, trust me.)
I'll make hotteok for you
in no time.
Coat it with oil.
(Applying some on his hands)
(Pulling)
(Adding lots of sugar)
He's good at cooking.
He has a knack for it.
Ji Hyeon is a good cook.
I wish there was something pretty
to press it with.
- What?
- What is that?
- You'll use the bottom of the mug?
- Yes.
I had nothing to press it with.
How smart.
(Sizzling)
Yes, it sounds pretty good.
- It worked.
- It turned out well.
I'm a genius cook.
I really like you.
Why?
Because you're so optimistic.
The look on his face...
- He's almost half-asleep.
- His soul left his body.
I didn't know
he was struggling so much.
- It must be somewhere there.
- Look how red his face is.
(Rummaging through, feeling faint)
(Throwing)
(Giving up the hand warmers
to the floor)
Oh, he removed the hand warmers.
Did you notice that he removed
the hand warmers or not?
- I bet he didn't.
- I don't think he knew.
I didn't know.
It's my first time seeing it.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'll make it delicious for you.
You did a good job.
It looks quite nice.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Gosh, you're good.
- It's not bad, right?
You have a knack for it.
Of course I do.
(Showing off his skill)
It's ready.
(Homemade winter snack
to spend winter)
Let's eat.
(Ji Hyeon, who worked hard,
has a bite first.)
(Amazed)
- It's good.
- It must be delicious.
(Laughing)
What? Hotteok is easy to make.
Yes, it's good. You did well.
(Heated table and hotteok)
(It's warm in the winter.)
(Exclaiming)
You can sell this too.
- Right?
- You can sell this too.
It's good. I was hungry.
Right?
It's warm.
You feel really good...
- after you sweat a lot.
- That's right.
That's what I was after, seriously.
- It relieves your stress.
- Detoxing.
It must be good.
(Another winter snack
to break a sweat)
(Inhaling heated energy)
They're having something spicy
when it's already heated.
It's good!
(Jae Soo also fills himself up
with heat.)
(Amazed)
I'm sure even Jae Soo's underwear
is wet.
(I'm sure even Jae Soo's underwear
is wet.)
(Breaking a sweat in earnest)
You must keep yourself warm
like this in winter.
I sweated too much.
(Is he heated up yet?)
I'll make that for you.
I discovered an amazing combination.
- What is it?
- Seriously.
He took out something cold
for the first time.
Oh, you're having ice cream?
- Watch, Jae Soo.
- Okay.
Like this...
(Added a touch of freshness
to the cool ice cream)
Seriously...
- Jae Soo...
- Where did you learn this?
Just try it, Jae Soo.
It's to die for.
You should eat it like this.
Yes. That's it. Great.
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
It's crazy, isn't it?
(Thrilled)
It's the best ice cream
I've had this year.
It's exactly like
griddle fried ice cream.
It's really good.
Because you were crazy hot.
The house itself was a griddle.
(Cooling ice cream
that's guaranteed to be good)
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
The strawberry is delicious.
Recently, I've been feeling...
really comfortable around
this neighborhood...
when I come home from work.
It finally feels like
my own neighborhood.
I have a friend I can rely on too.
I think I'll be happy in the winter
if I continue to spend it like this.
I think it'll be warm.
Do you want to go
to a sauna in the evening?
- Tonight?
- Yes.
- You want to go to a sauna too?
- Let's go and...
- But we are in a sauna.
Is that so?
Don't catch a cold
in the winter, seriously.
(I Stayed Warm All Winter)
(Next story)
(Rainbow Running Horses Special,
Part 3)
(Peeking)
(Someone makes her bed
as soon as she wakes up.)
(I've been living alone
for 7 years.)
(I'm the baby beast, Kim Si Hyeon.)
(Roar)
(The cute scene-stealer
from "Culinary Class Wars 2")
(She made a lasting impression
with skillful hands.)
(Chef Kim Si Hyeon
with unexpected charisma)
(Introducing the brand new home)
(Inside the neat house)
(Attention-grabbing)
(A huge cabinet
that fills the whole living room)
(The kitchen tools she collected
for 7 years)
(Treasure trove)
(She quickly puts on a jacket.)
(Then she worries
about her outfit for today?)
(What completes her style
is her shopping cart.)
(She heads to the market
with her dotted shopping cart.)
(Friendly)
(She diligently eats too.)
(The ultimate social butterfly
of this area)
(Her target for today
is a vegetable buffet?)
(It's me, baby beast.)
(Siler divaricata, pine mushroom,)
(poplar mushroom...)
(Do you have mugwort too?)
(Enthusiastic vegetable hunt)
(Plentiful)
(Korea has namul,
seasoned vegetables.)
(She cuts and stir-fries them.)
(The possibilities with vegetables
are endless.)
(This is indeed so much fun.)
(Why doesn't it work?)
(I'll heal myself with ramyeon.)
(Slurping)
(This is delicious.)
(Herbivore Baby Beast)
(Chacha)
(Ja Yeon spends her day
with Chacha, as usual.)
(Bom)
(I adopted a second cat.)
(Lively...)
(and full of curiosity and love)
(I'm Bom.)
(The cat can't see.)
(Ja Yeon found her
on the cold street.)
(They became family like fate.)
(I can do whatever I want
even if I can't see.)
(Watch me hanging.)
(Hanging)
(Welcome, a new family member!)
(Another new bond)
(A table tennis club
at her apartment complex)
(I find table tennis really fun.)
(Namyangju's queen of table tennis,
Ok Table Tennis)
(Laughing)
(Make it natural.)
(You're good.)
(If you compliment me...)
(The seniors shower her with love.)
(Ok Table Tennis...)
(enters the court.)
Let's go!
(Yes, I'm Ok Table Tennis!)
(Ok Table Tennis' Dream
Will Come True)